tezaktrafficpower.com 2019-03-30

# Tezzers

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Tezzers uses and protects any information that you give Tezzers when you use this website. 

Tezzers is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Tezzers will never sell, rent, or lease any information contained in your membership profile. 

Information obtained about you for the purpose of creating your Tezzers membership shall be used only for the purpose of maintaining and updating your membership, as well as direct email contact from Tezzers and your Tezzers upline/downline (if you allow this in your profile). 

Tezzers reserves the right to investigate using any and all means necessary, should there be reason to believe unauthorized transactions are processed in your name. We will then take every precaution possible to protect our members from identify theft both here at Tezzers and elsewhere. 

Tezzers may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 11/03/16. 

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information: 

  * name and other personal information you might provide in your profile 
  * contact information including email address 
  * Information about your network/computer including IP address and browser type 
  * Date and time of your visits and registration and where you came from 
  * Information about your activity on the website 
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests 
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers 

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Internal record keeping. 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests. 

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

Ads appearing on our or our members websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Tezzers and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to [disable/decline cookies](http://www.wikihow.com/Disable-Cookies) if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: 

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes 
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by clicking the Unsubscribe link provided in each email, or emailing us at krmhelp@gmail.com or by contacting us at the [help desk](http://akhmediagroup.com/supportdesk/home/70/Tezzers%20Traffic%20Power.html). 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us at krmhelp@gmail.com or contact us at the [help desk](http://akhmediagroup.com/supportdesk/home/70/Tezzers%20Traffic%20Power.html). 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

**Kids Privacy Act**

Tezzers supports the U.S. federal regulations on children's privacy. This means that we will not keep your personal information on record. If you contact us in the future, we will not be able to refer back to this message. 

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILD ONLINE PRIVACY ACT (COPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO. 

**Business Transfer**

If Tezzers, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Tezzers goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Tezzers or any of its site or services may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

**Contact**

Contact us here if you have any questions. 

Help Desk: [Contact Us](http://akhmediagroup.com/supportdesk/home/70/Tezzers%20Traffic%20Power.html)

By Email: krmhelp@gmail.com 

Please also refer to our Terms of Service again if needed.
